http://www.westminstercollection.com/privacy-cookie-policy.aspx

We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue without changing your settings, we'll assume that you are happy to receive all cookies on the Westminster Collection.
Brand
Toggle navigation
Menu
Help
Blog
CoinsBritish Isles202020192018Previous yearsSovereignsHistoric CoinsSilver A-Z 10psEncapsulated A-Z 10psRoyal Mint BU PacksRoyal Mint Proof SetsBy CountryCanadaUSAAustraliaChinaFranceJerseyGuernseyBy ThemeHarry PotterVE Day 75th AnniversaryPeter Pan 50p50 Years of the 50pBeatrix PotterRoyaltyMilitaryAviationRoyal British LegionDinosaursGift RangeAccessoriesVE Day 50psDateStamp (TM)Silver and morePresentation CasesSilver CoinsCollector's GalleryHomeSmall GoldStar WarsMarvelACDCWildlifeGothicSpaceSnowman 50pPopular ThemesDinosaur 50pBrexitHarry PotterVE Day 75th AnniversaryPeter PanRupert Bear 50pChange CheckerCERTIFIED BU CoinsFifty PenceTwo PoundsOne PoundFive PoundsA-Z 10psA-Z Early Strike 10psSilver A-Z 10psEncapsulated A-Z 10psCirculating CoinsUKBritish IslesA-Z Early Strike 10psTheme2020 CoinsBeatrix PotterPaddingtonRoyaltyInternationalChristmas CardsHistoric UK Coins and BanknotesBanknotesPre-decimal CoinsOut of Circulation CoinsAlbums and AccessoriesAlbumsAccessoriesCollector PacksChange Checker+Wallets, Pages and ID CardsChange Checker Shop HomeRoyal Mint PacksInternational CoinsTop 10MedalsBy ThemeHarry PotterFilm & TVBeatrix PotterAviationMilitaryTransport & Space TravelRoyalty & British HistorySeasonalStampsBy ThemeBlockbuster & TV ReleasesMARVEL Comics StampsRoyaltyMilitaryCelebrations and CommemorationsAccessoriesSherlockHistoric Stamps - by MonarchVictoriaEdward VIIGeorge VGeorge VIQEIIHistoric Stamps - by CountryGreat Britain & CommonwealthUSA & CanadaFranceSouth AfricaAustraliaFramed Vinyl ClassicsBlogHelp
The Westminster Collection Privacy Policy
In line with the General Data Protection Regulation our Privacy Policy is governed by the following five principles. We will…
1. Always work to keep data safe.
2. Make it clear when and why we are collecting data.
3. Keep data up to date and only hold it for as long as necessary.
4. Only hold data for the purpose it was collected.
5. Treat data with the same respect you treat your own personal data.
Updating your communications preferences:
Please visit the Contact Preferences Centre if you would like to amend how you hear from us.
The detail
The Westminster Collection is a trading style of 288 Group Ltd. who are registered under the Data Protection Act. You can contact us at data.protection@westminstercollection.com with any questions.
We collect and securely store the customer information you provide, including payment preferences, to provide you with the goods, services and information expected of a mail-order / online retail company.
We use your information for the purposes of marketing coins, stamps and other collectibles which are of interest to you.
How we collect data
We collect and process data on the basis of legitimate interest. This will be whenever you enter into a transaction with us or manage your account. We also collect data when you complete other interactions such as entering a competition or applying for a job.
If we collect data which can be used to contact you, we will always offer you choices for managing your communication preferences, explained further in the 'Marketing Communication' section below.
We, and some of our business partners, also collect information when you browse our website or blog, which is explained below in the 'Marketing Communications' and 'Cookie Policy' sections.
Keeping your data
We make sure to only keep data for as long as it is required to service your account, retain your transactional history and remember your preferences. We also hold certain types of data in accordance with legal requirements for tax and accounting rules.
It's important to us that your details are as up to date as possible.
You can edit your personal details here or contact our Customer Service Team here.
How we keep your data secure
As appropriate we use comprehensive modern technology and processes to ensure the security of all data held, including but not limited to: firewalls; encryption, anonymization, password management and regular software updates. We perform a regular review to make sure our security measures match the level of sensitivity of the data held. We only retain data for the length of time it is required as detailed in the section above.
Marketing Communications
If you are a customer we might contact you by email, mail or telephone unless you ask us not to.
You can choose at any time not to be contacted and we will update your preferences.
You can do this by updating your contact preferences here or by contacting our Customer Service Team.
If you inform us that you no longer wish to receive marketing emails and/or telephone calls you will stop receiving them within 24 hours. We will still hold your email address (unless you ask us to remove it) to contact you about customer service related issues - despatch updates for example.
If you inform us you no longer wish to receive postal marketing you may still receive some letters up to 4 weeks after you change your preferences as mailings are printed in advance. You will still receive customer service related letters.
If you have indicated that you are happy for us to do so, we occasionally share data with carefully selected 3rd parties so they can contact you. You can opt out by updating your contact preferences here or by contacting the Customer Service Team.
We advertise using many internet based platforms, including Facebook, Twitter, Google Ads and others. We make sure we always act in accordance with the terms and conditions of these platforms to show you products and news you may be interested in. All of these platforms offer you ways to manage your privacy and advertising preferences from within their own settings.
We may also share your personal information and limited transactional data with business partners to help target the offers we make to you such as Google; feedback sites including Feefo and Trustpilot, suppliers we engage to process data on our behalf such as Neverbounce; data co-operatives such as Epsilon Abacus; Government bodies and law enforcement agencies (if required to do so), and successors in title to our business.
Re-targeting (also known as re-marketing)
We use re-targeting to show customers and visitors to our website tailored adverts served by 3rd party vendors across the internet. We work with partners such as Google and Facebook to do this using first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the Double Click cookie). To learn more, or to opt-out of receiving online display advertisements tailored to your interests by our third party partners, visit the Network Advertising Initiative at www.networkadvertising.org/choices.
Epsilon Abacus
We work with Epsilon Abacus (registered as Epsilon International UK Ltd), a company that manages the Abacus Alliance on behalf of UK retailers. The participating retailers are active in the clothing, collectables, food & wine, gardening, gadgets & entertainment, health & beauty, household goods, and home interiors categories. They share information on what their customers buy. Epsilon Abacus analyses this pooled information to help the retailers understand consumers' wider buying patterns. From this information, retailers can tailor their communications, sending people suitable offers that should be of interest to them, based on what they like to buy.
Please note that Epsilon Abacus may transfer data outside the EEA. The transfer will take place in the presence of appropriate safeguards, including standard data protection clauses adopted by the EU Commission. If you would like more information, please email us at data.protection@westminstercollection.com .
Cookies
Cookies are text files that are automatically placed onto your device by many websites. They are used to improve the performance of a website, for remembering preferences, for making your experience on a site smoother and to provide website owners with information on how the site is being used.
We use cookies to enhance your experience of our website and blog, to identify and monitor how the website is being used and to track how our advertisements perform.
To enjoy the full experience of our website, and to make a purchase, you will need to allow cookies.
However, to get a better understanding of how to get control of cookies on your system we suggest you go to www.aboutcookies.org - they have lots of up-to-date information about how to manage cookies in the latest internet browsers.
Contacting us
We welcome your comments and messages. For general enquiries or account based questions please contact us here.
For questions or comments about our privacy policy please email data.protection@westminstercollection.com.
Back to top
